# **Andrew Giovanni Winoto**

# UNDERGRADUATE STUDENT

# Tangerang | andrewgiovanniw@gmail.com | 08119200850

#### **About Me**

I'm an undergraduate Information System BINUS University Undergraduate student who is experienced in multiple programming languages such as PHP, Java, React, Swift, MySQL, etc. I am dedicated to leveraging my skills and knowledge to contribute to the field of software development.

# Job Experience

#### **Laboratory Teaching Assistant – Part Time**

Feb 2022 - July 2022

- Mastered programming languages from teaching multiple programming classes.
- Delivering programming courses to BINUS University students.

## Laboratory Teaching Assistant – Full Time

September 2022 - Feb 2024

• Completed game creation, web development, mobile application development, and desktop application developments projects.

# **Organization Experience**

#### **BINUS HIMSISFO Activist**

Jan 2022 - Jan 2023

- Organizing and managing events for BINUS University Information System students.
- Selected as Vice Coordinator of SELCAVIS 2022

## **Volunteer Experience**

#### Teach For Indonesia & KMBD – DVSOS Campaign Volunteer

Mar 2022 - Mar 2022

Creating educational videos for people with autism to help them read, write, and count.

## Teach For Indonesia Volunteer Social Media Campaign Aku untuk Hijau Bumiku

2021

Creating a social media campaign to raise community awareness of green earth.

### Teach For Indonesia Volunteer Sosialisasi Anti-Rasisme Kepada Anak Panti Asuhan

2021

Planning and organizing visits to orphanages to support and provide their basic daily needs.

# **Education**

# **Bina Nusantara University**

2021 - Present

• Information System Undergraduate – CGPA 3.84

# **SMAK Penabur Gading Serpong**

2018 - 2021

• Science Study

# **Skills & abilities**

- Swift
- PHP
- HTML, CSS, JS
- Java
- ReactJS, NextronJS
- C, C++, C#
- Python
- MySqL, SQLServer